Hey, Ross.
嘿，罗斯
I'm so glad someone's here. Could you zip me up?
真高兴有人在这里 你可以帮我把拉链拉起来吗？
- Sure. - Thank you.
-当然可以 -谢谢
Can you believe no one between my apartment and here..
你相信从我家到这里的路上…
offered to do that for me?
竟然没有人愿意帮我拉拉链吗？
People.
真是的
So why are you so dressed up?
你穿这么漂亮做什么呢？
Mike's picking me up for a date.
麦克要来接我去约会
How's that going? Is it getting serious?
交往得如何呢？ 是不是越来越认真了？
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I like him.
我不知道，我不知道 我是蛮喜欢他的
But am I ready to take my Grade A loins off the meat market?
但是我还没有准备好要退出江湖
I'm not quite sure.
我不太确定
You know, I really admire your whole dating attitude.
我真的很欣赏你的约会态度
It's so healthy. I'm always like, "Is this moving too fast?
真是很健康的态度 我总是在想会不会进展太快了？…
Is this moving too slow? Where's this going?"
会不会进展太慢了？ 这将怎么发展呢？
I know. You are a bit of a drama queen.
我知道 你就像是个戏剧女王
You're so much better off. You just go from guy to guy having fun..
你真是太厉害了 男朋友一个接着一个 享受乐趣...
and not worrying that it never turns into anything serious.
完全不担心没有结局
I wouldn't say "never."
我不敢说“完全不”
You know, there is that guy.
有一次有个男的…
Okay, well, what about..?
好的，哪个…？
Okay, there's gotta be someone.
总该有个人吧
- There isn't! That's what I'm saying. - Oh, my God, you're right!
-根本就没有！我就说吧 -喔，天啊，你说的没错！
I know. And yet, here you are, all ready for the next date.
我知道，一段恋情才刚结束 马上又可以跟其他人约会
I can't believe I never realized this before.
真不敢相信 我之前都没有注意到这点
I'm in my 30s, and I've never been in a long-term relationship.
我已经三十几岁了 从来没有爱情长跑过
Oh, my God, what's wrong with me?
喔，天啊，我是有什么毛病？
There's nothing wrong with you.
你没有什么毛病
I mean, you don't strike me as the type of person that wants to get married.
我是说，你不像那种 看起来会想结婚的人
I want to get married!
我想结婚！
No, please.. Please don't cry because of me.
别这样，拜托…别因为我而哭
I don't know what I'm talking about, okay? I've been divorced three times.
我根本不知道我在说什么 我离婚三次了
At least you've been married.
至少你结过婚
Oh, my God! I want to trade lives with Ross?!
喔，我的天啊！ 我竟然羡慕起罗斯了？
Phoebe.
菲比
- What's wrong? - Nothing. I'm excited about our date.
-怎么了？ -没事，要跟你约会太兴奋了
Mike, this is Ross Geller. Ross, this is Mike..
麦克，这位是罗斯盖勒 罗斯，这位是麦克…
- Sorry, I didn't catch that. - Mike Hanigan.
-对不起，我没有听清楚 -麦克汉尼根
- Ross Geller. - Hey.
-罗斯盖勒 -嘿
So are you sure you're ready to go?
你确定准备好了吗？
How do I look?
我看起来怎样？
- Do you have a compact in your purse? - No.
-你皮包里有小镜子吗？ -没有
You look great.
你看起来棒透了
The One With The Sharks
本集播出：鲨鱼
rianystar压制iPod-MP4
- Hey, Joey. - This girl won't turn around.
-嘿，乔伊 -那个女的就是不转过来
I can't tell if she's hot or not. What do you think?
我无法判断她是不是很辣 你觉得呢？
Joey, I am not going to objectify women with you.
乔伊，我不会跟你一起把女性物化的
But if her face is as nice as her ass..
但是如果她的脸 跟她的屁股一样棒的话…
- Mama! - All right. Thanks.
-妈妈咪啊！ -好的，谢谢
- Have you talked to Chandler? - He has to stay in Tulsa this weekend.
-你有跟钱德讲电话了吗？ -他这周末要留在土尔沙
- How come? - I don't know. He has to work.
-为什么？ -我不知道，有工作要做
There's some big rush on the..
要赶那个…
Damn it. I'm gonna have to start listening when he talks about his job.
讨厌！我应该要开始 认真听他讲工作的事了
Why don't you fly out there and surprise him?
你何不飞过去给他个惊喜呢？
I'd love to. I really miss him.
我很想啊，我真的很想念他
But I can't. I have one day off and it's just too expensive.
但是不行，我只有放一天假 而且机票太贵了
Interesting. So Chandler's not worth the price of a plane ticket to you.
真好玩，所以机票钱 比钱德还重要
Of course he is.
当然是钱德较重要
Maybe I will go.
或许我应该飞过去
We'll have a little second honeymoon at the Tulsa Ramada.
我们可以在土尔沙的饭店 来个二度小蜜月
You should bring your black see-through teddy with the attached garters.
你应该带你那件黑色透明性感内衣 加上吊带裤袜
- How do you know I have one of those? - Didn't until just now.
-你怎么知道我有那件呢？ -本来不知道，现在知道了
Hot. Not hot.
辣，不辣
Hot!
辣！
Excuse me?
什么？
I said that I think you're hot.
我说我觉得你很辣
And.. now I'm embarrassed.
而…现在我糗死了
I thought you said "hi."
我以为你是说“嗨”
That would've been better.
如果是那样就好了
I'll try that. Hi, I'm Joey.
我来试试看，嗨，我是乔伊
I'm Hayley.
我是海莉
Look, I don't normally ask out women that I meet in coffeehouses.
通常我不约在咖啡店遇到的女生出去
Gesundheit.
保重
But..
但是…
This is hard. I'm kind of shy.
真是很难开口，我有点害羞
Seriously, you should see someone about that cold.
真的，你应该去看医生的
If it gets much worse, you could die.
如果感冒越来越严重，你可是会死的
- Anyway.. - I would love to go out with you.
-反正… -我很乐意跟你出去
Really? Great.
真的吗？太棒了
Did I..? Did I actually ask you?
我有…我有开口约你吗？
That's just where you were going. I figured I'd help you out.
由你说话的方式 我就猜得到你要做什么
You don't seem like the kind of guy who does this a lot?
你不像是那种经常这样的男生吧？
Damn it, Gunther, you gave it to me.
真是的，阿甘，你传染给我了
Oh, it's you.
喔，是你
With vegetarian corndogs.
我带了素食热狗
Come on, I just want to talk to you.
别这样，我只想跟你说说话
About what? How few ova I have left?
说什么？说我还剩下几个卵子吗？
Come on, I just wanna apologize for what happened yesterday.
别这样，我只想为昨天发生的事道歉
I'm sorry, Phoebe.
我很抱歉，菲比
That's okay, Ross.
没关系，罗斯
- So how'd the date go? - Well, it was awful.
-约会还好吗？ -糟透了
I barely got through dinner.
我几乎撑不过晚餐
Every time I thought about what you said, I cried.
每次我想到你说的话，我就哭了
I'm pretty sure he spent most of the night just staring at me in horror.
我非常肯定他整晚都惊恐的盯着我看
But I couldn't know for sure because my eyes were swollen shut.
但是我无法真的确定 因为我的眼睛已经肿到张不开了
You know I wasn't trying to make you cry.
你知道我不是故意要惹你哭的
I was really trying to say something nice.
我本来是想要说一些很好听的话的
I was basically saying even though you've never been in a serious relationship..
我只是要说，即使你 从未有过认真的感情…
- Are we gonna do this again? - Sorry.
-我们还要再讨论这个吗？ -对不起
- So he hasn't called? - Would you call this girl:
-他还没打来吗？ -你会打给这种女的吗？
"Thanks for.. a lovely.. evening"?
“谢谢…美好…一晚”
Now I feel terrible. This is all my fault.
我觉得糟透了 这全都是我的错
You know what you should feel terrible about?
你知道更糟的是什么吗？
This could have been my serious guy.
这男的有可能是可以认真的对象
He was sweet and smart and funny.
他很体贴、聪明又风趣
You know how hard it is to meet a guy like that?
你知道要遇到这样的男生有多难吗？
We are a rare breed.
我们的确是稀有动物
Hey, maybe that's him.
嘿，可能就是他哦
Hello?
喂？
Could you hold on one sec?
你可以等一下吗？
- I need some privacy. - Is it Mike?
-我需要一点隐私 -是不是麦克呢？
No, it's a heavy breather. I'll take what I can get.
不，是骚扰电话 我现在什么都接了
I'm listening.
我在线上
What a great dinner.
晚餐实在太棒了
Thanks again for letting me have that last piece of cake at the restaurant.
再次谢谢你让我吃最后一块蛋糕
You're welcome again. I'm gonna go make some coffee.
不用客气，我要去煮咖啡
- Can I get you anything? - Do you have any cake?
-你要什么呢？ -你有蛋糕吗？
So this is going pretty good.
真是进行的太顺利了
Dinner was nice. We've got a lot in common.
晚餐很棒，我们有许多共同点
Victoria 's Secret.
“维多莉亚的秘密”(性感内衣目录)
We even like the same books.
我们甚至喜欢相同的书
There's a scary painting.
这幅画真可怕
Wait a minute.
等等
I think I've been scared by that painting before.
我记得好像被这幅画给吓过
You know what? This whole place looks familiar.
你知道吗？ 这地方看起来真眼熟
I have definitely been in this apartment.
我一定曾经来过这里
I know I've seen this weird plant before.
我看过这棵可怕的植物
It did that the last time!
它上次也是这样刺我！
Oh, my God. I've gone out with this girl before.
喔，天啊 我跟这个女的约会过
Yeah! We had sex on this couch!
没错！我们在这沙发上做过爱！
And then on that chair, and.. No.
然后在那张椅子上 还有…，不对
No, we didn't do it here..
不对，没有在这里…
which is weird, because it seems like a perfectly good place.
这倒是很奇怪，看起来超适合的
That's why.
这就是为什么
Hey, Mike. Sorry to just drop by like this. Can I come in?
嘿，麦克，很抱歉这样跑过来 我可以进来吗？
Sure.
当然
Who are you?
你是谁呢？
I'm Ross. Phoebe's friend from the coffeehouse?
我是罗斯，菲比在咖啡屋的朋友
I really, really need to talk to you about something.
我真的非常需要跟你谈一件事
Unless..
除非…
You're not gonna try and get me to join a cult, are you?
你不是要拉我信什么教吧？
No, it's just, you know, you have that look.
没啦，因为，你知道的 你长得很像那种人
Damn Supercuts!
该死的199剪发！
- Well, what's up? Is Phoebe okay? - Oh, yeah, yeah.
-怎么回事呢？菲比还好吗？ -喔，还好，还好
Phoebe is great. But..
菲比很好，但是…
I'm an idiot, okay?
我是个蠢蛋
Right before you guys went out..
就在你们出去约会前…
I accidentally got her all upset.
我不小心惹得她很难过
That's why she was weird.
难怪她不对劲
Yes. Yeah, I..
是的，是啊，我…
Yeah, I said something stupid about her never having had a serious relationship.
我说了些蠢话，关于她从没有过 认真的恋爱关系等等
But you should know, she is so much fun. A wonderful person.
但是你应该知道，她是很风趣的 很棒的一个人
- Please, don't blow her off. - I'm not gonna blow her off.
-拜托，别将她判出局 -我不会判她出局的
I just spoke to her. We're going out tomorrow night.
我才刚跟她说完电话 我们明晚要出去
I mean, I hope that's okay with you, stranger from the coffeehouse.
我是说，如果你没有意见的话 咖啡屋的陌生人
That's great. So the crying didn't turn you off?
太棒了，所以她狂哭并没有吓跑你？
I just got out of a nine-year relationship with a manic-depressive.
我刚刚跟一个躁郁症患者 结束九年的恋情
Compared to that, Phoebe's a Mousketeer.
跟她相比，菲比根本是只小猫
Well, then, I didn't need to bother you.
好吧，那我就不需要再打扰你了
You or the four other Mike Hanigans I bothered.
你，外加四个麦克汉尼根 都被我打扰了
One of whom was quite large and a little flirty.
其中一个还很高壮 有点爱打情骂俏
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Is that true what you said?
等等，等等 你刚刚说的是真的吗？
Phoebe's never had a serious relationship?
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱？
Of course she has.
她当然有过
If she's never had a serious relationship..
如果她没有谈过认真的恋爱…
do you think I'd go around broadcasting it..
你认为我会到处去广播…
like some kind of unstoppable moron?
像是无法克制的白痴一样 见人就说吗？
- But you did say it. - Yes. Yes, I did.
-但是你的确是那样说了 -是的，是的，我是说了
And I will also say..
而且我还会说…
what I'm about to say..
我接下来要说的…
vis-a-vis..
相对于…
the following.
以下的说法
Phoebe has never had a serious relationship..
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱…
since..
是从…
her super-serious relationship..
她超级认真地…
with..
跟…
Vikram.
伟软分手之后
- Vikram? - What? That's a real name.
-伟软？ -怎样？那是真的名字
Stop it!
停停吧！
Why couldn't they have sent me to Texas?
为什么不是派我去德州呢？
Seven o'clock.
七点钟
Maybe I'll hit the gym.
或许我该去健身房
Who am I kidding? Pay-per-view porn.
少来了，还是看情色频道好了
- Do not disturb! Do not disturb! - Surprise!
-不要打扰！不要打扰！ -惊喜吧！
- Monica? - Is everything all right?
-摩妮卡？ -一切都还好吧？
Yeah, everything's great. I was just..
是啊，一切都很好 我刚刚…
watching some regular television there.
在看一些正常的电视节目
What a pleasant surprise.
这个惊喜真是太令人兴奋了
- I'm gonna go freshen up, okay? - Okay, honey.
-我去梳洗一下，好吗？ -好的，亲爱的
That was close.
差一点点
- Hello. - Hey, Rach, it's me.
-喂 -嘿，瑞秋，是我
Okay, I just got to Chandler's room, and I caught him..
我刚到钱德的房间 然后看到他…
molesting himself.
正在自摸
That couldn't have been pretty.
那划面可能不是很好看
But you know, guys do that.
但是你知道的，男生常那样做的
Well, the weird part is..
但是，很奇怪的是…
he was getting off.. to a shark-attack show!
他在看的是鲨鱼攻击影片耶！
- No! - Yes! Chandler watches shark porn!
-好恶！ -是的！钱德竟然在看鲨鱼色情片！
- While watching sharks? - Yeah.
-在看鲨鱼的时候？ -是啊
Are you sure that's what he was doing?
你确定他是在做那档事吗？
You know how many times I've seen him jump up like that?
你知道我看他 那样跳起来过多少次了吗？
Believe me, I know what he was doing.
相信我，我知道他在做什么
Man! Sharks!
天啊！鲨鱼！
I always knew there was something weird about that dude.
我就知道那个人有地方不对劲
You promised to love him no matter what.
你发誓过无论如何都要爱他的
"What" means, like, if he gets a disease or kills someone.
“无论如何”讲的是像如果他得病 还是杀了人什么的
Not if he gets his jollies to Jaws.
而不是如果 他把小弟弟放到鲨鱼嘴里
You know what, honey? Guys are just different.
你知道吗？亲爱的 男生是很不一样的
They like things that we can't understand.
他们喜欢一些我们无法理解的东西
I once dated this guy who wanted to pretend..
我曾经约会过一个男的 总是想要假装…
that he was an archeologist, and I was this..
他是考古学家 而我是…
naughty cavewoman who he unfroze from a block of ice.
他从冰块中解救出来 调皮的山顶洞女人
Are you talking about my brother?
你是在说我哥吗？
I didn't disguise that very well, did I?
我装得不像，对不对？
- Hey. - Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
I went out with this girl last night. Halfway through our date I realized..
我昨晚跟一个女孩子出去 我到一半的时候才发现…
I already slept with her.
我已经跟她上过床了
You've slept with all the women in N.Y., and now you're going around again?
所以你已经跟全纽约的女人上过床了 现在只是从头开始再来一次？
That's not even the weird part.
这还不是最奇怪的地方
- She didn't remember sleeping with me! - You don't remember sleeping with her.
-她竟然不记得跟我上过床了！ -你也不记得跟她上过床啊
But she should remember sleeping with me. I am very memorable!
但是她应该要记得的 我可是很令人难忘的！
- You guys know. - How do we know?
-你们知道的 -我们怎么会知道呢？
- We've never slept with you. - And whose fault is that?
-我们又没有跟你上过床 -那是谁的错呢？
What's the big deal? You forgot, she forgot.
又没有什么大不了的 你忘了，她忘了
- Maybe you were having an off night. - Hey!
-或许那天晚上你没有达阵！ -嘿！
I never have an off night. Okay?
我向来都有达阵的，好吗？
Although, sometimes if I'm a little bloated, I don't feel that sexy.
虽然有时候如果我吃太胀 可能就不会觉得很性感
But even then, I'm better than most!
但是即使是那样，我都比别人强！
Honey, why don't you just let it go and ask her out again?
亲爱的，你何不就此释怀 再约她出去呢？
You're both so slutty, you don't remember who you slept with.
你们都是骚货 你们根本都不记得跟谁上过床
You're made for each other.
你们是天生的一对
Interesting.
真有趣
Well, I'll go out with her again and I'll try to get past it.
好吧，我会再跟她出去 然后忘了过去
No salt! Bloaty!
不吃盐！会胀气！
- Joey? - What?
-乔伊？ -干嘛？
You don't think sharks are sexy, do you?
你会觉得鲨鱼很性感吗？
No.
不会
Wait a minute. Wait, what was the Little Mermaid?
等一下，等等 小美人鱼是鲨鱼吗？
It's open!
门没锁！
- Hey. - Mike called! We're going out again!
-嘿 -麦克打电话来了，我们要再约会了！
Quick thing. I went to talk to Mike.
一件小事，我去找麦克谈过
What?
什么？
What did you..? What did you do, Ross?
你做…？ 你做了什么？罗斯
Oh, boy. You got mad at that part.
喔，天啊，光这样你就生气了
I went over there, you know, to tell him how..
我过去找他，告诉他…
How great you are. But..
你是个很棒的人，但是…
Well, you know me. Blah-blah-blah.
嗯，你知道我的，话太多了
- And I ended up telling him that.. - What?
-然后我最后竟然告诉他… -什么？
You had a six-year-long relationship..
你有过六年的恋情…
with a guy named Vikram.
跟一个叫做伟软的人
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
Well, he seemed..
因为，他…
to bum hard when I told him you'd never been in a serious relationship.
在我说你从未谈过 认真的恋情之后，好像有点惊讶
If you hadn't just had a baby with my best friend..
如果你不是刚跟我 最要好的朋友生下小孩
I swear to Lucifer..
我跟撒旦发誓…
a rabid dog would be feasting on your danglers right now!
一只狂犬病疯狗正要吃掉 你裤档里的那根东西了！
I think you'll feel differently when you know..
我想如果你知道多一点关于伟软的事…
a little bit about Vikram.
你会感觉好多了
Okay, he's a..
好的，他是…
He's a kite designer.
他是风筝设计师
And he used to date Oprah.
而且他曾经跟于美人约会过
I'm not going along with some lie you made up, Ross.
我不会跟你唱双簧说谎的，罗斯
- I'm just gonna be honest with him. - Good.
-我会跟他老实说 -很好
Just be honest with him.
跟他老实说
- I have nothing to be ashamed of. - No.
-我没有什么好隐瞒的 -没错
So I haven't been in a relationship that lasted longer than a month.
就算我的每段感情 都没有超过一个月…
Okay? I haven't had a real boyfriend.
那又如何呢？是啊 我是没有过真正的男朋友
If he can't handle it, then he can leave. Which he will.
如果他无法接受 那他可以离开，我想他会离开的
And, you know, that's okay. So I'll just be alone forever.
而这一切都没有关系 我只不过会永远孤单而已
You know, all right. It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
都没关系了，一切都会没事的
I'll go on walking tours with widows and lesbians.
我就跟寡妇还有同性恋一起出去玩嘛
- I'll get it. - Okay.
-我去开门 -好的
I'm trying to remember the last time I opened a door and you weren't there.
让我想想有哪一次，开门的人不是你
Phoebe, are you okay?
菲比，你还好吗？
Yeah. There's just..
还好，只不过是…
There's something you should know.
有件事你必须要知道
Vikram just called.
伟软刚打电话来
So it was really a shock after 25 years of marriage..
所以在经历二十五年的婚姻之后 这真是很让人惊讶
my parents getting divorced. I took it the hardest..
我的模范父母竟然要离婚 我真的很难接受
- because I was the youngest. - Sure. Yeah.
-因为我是老么 -当然
How can you not remember me?
你怎么会忘了我是谁？
What?
什么？
How could you not remember that we slept together?
你怎么会忘了我们上过床？
- What? When? - I don't know!
-什么？何时？ -我不知道！
I really, really think I would remember sleeping with you.
我真的、真的认为 如果有我会记得的
Come on, come on. Search your brain, all right? It was..
快点，快点 仔细回想，好吗？那就在…
a certain amount of time ago. I was here. You were here.
之前某个时候 我在这里，你在这里
We had sex here, here, here..
我们在这里，这里，这里…
Not there.
没有那里，嘿咻
- Anything? - No, it's not ringing any bells.
-想起来了吗？ -没，一点印象也没有
My God, woman!
天啊，女人！
How many people have you been with not to remember this?
你跟多少人上过床 让你根本不记得我？
Hey, Hayley. We really gotta fix that doorknob.
嘿，海莉 我们真的要修理那个门把了
Joey?
乔伊？
I slept with you!
我跟你上过床！
And you obviously remember me! Hey, I still got it!
而且很明显的你记得我！ 嘿，表示我还不赖！
So we're good.
所以我们还好嘛
I'll let myself out.
我自己出去
And I said, "Okay, Vikram..
然后我说，伟软…
you can't just call every time you get lonely.
你不能每次寂寞就打电话给我
You gave up that right when you slept with Rachel."
在你跟瑞秋上床之后 你就没有那个权力了
Rachel? I thought she just had a baby with Ross.
瑞秋？我以为她才刚生下罗斯的小孩
Yeah, well..
是啊，嗯…
Yeah.
是啊
But Emma's birth certificate might say "Geller"..
艾犸的出生证明上或许生父是罗斯…
but her eyes say "Mukherjee."
但是她长得像伟软
That is so wrong. And on top of that, he's a glue sniffer?
这实在太糟了 而且他还吸强力胶？
I know. But he calls, and my heart goes to him.
我知道，但是他打来时 我的心就飞向他了
You know, that bastard is one smooth-talking freelance kite designer.
你知道的，那个浑蛋是个很会 说话的风筝设计师
If you want, I'll mess him up for you.
如果你要的话，我可以帮你修理他
You would do that?
真的吗？
Unless he's big. If he's really big, I'll send him..
除非他很大只 如果他真的很大只，我会给他…
a rude letter.
一封信，骂死他
I think there's somebody better out there for you.
我想有更好的人在等着你
I mean, you know, I'm.. I'm not saying me, but..
我是说，你知道的，我… 我不是指我，但是…
Maybe.. me.
或许…是我
And you don't have to worry about glue-sniffing with me.
而且你不用担心我会吸强力胶
Although, I do smell the occasional Magic Marker.
虽然有时候我会闻马克笔的味道
Yeah. Anyway, I just..
是啊，反正，我只是…
I think I can make you happy.
我想我可以让你快乐
- Okay, I can't do this. - What's wrong?
-好了，我办不到 -怎么了？
Well, there is no Vikram. Ross made him up.
根本没有伟软这个人 罗斯乱扯的
Because I..
因为我…
I really never have been in a long-term relationship.
我从未有过爱情长跑
I've never lived with a guy. I've never even celebrated an anniversary.
我从未跟男人同居过 从来没有庆祝交往一周年
So..
所以…
If that's too weird for you..
如果这对你而言太奇怪…
and you want to leave, I understand.
所以你想现在就走人 我可以理解
In fact, I'll close my eyes to make it less awkward.
事实上，我要闭上双眼 让这一切不至于太尴尬
You kissed me.
你亲了我
- You don't think I'm a total freak? - No.
-你不认为我是怪人吗？ -不
Well..
那么…
Look, can I..?
那，我可不…？
Can I think you're a little weird and also cool..
我可不可以认为你有点怪 但又有点酷…
for telling me the truth and also want to kiss you?
因为你告诉我事情的真相 而且让我想亲你？
I guess so.
我想应该可以
Can I think it's cool that you kissed me..
我可不可以认为，你亲我真是很酷…
and also want to kiss you again?
而且我想要亲回去？
And be a little concerned about the Magic Markers?
有一点担心马克笔的事可以吗？
Definitely.
当然可以
This is Vikram.
我是伟软
I need to talk to you about the long-term relationship we had.
我需要跟你谈我们之间 那段长期的恋情
Call me. I am in my kite-making studio.
回电给我，我在我的风筝工作室
Hi, honey, I'm home.
嗨，亲爱的，我回来了
Hi.
嗨
- How was your flight? - It was great.
-旅途还好吗？ -不错
I ordered a pool float from the Sky Mall.
我从飞机上的购物目录订了浮板
Why'd I do that?
为什么我要订呢？
Why don't you sit down.
过来坐下吧
Get yourself comfortable.
放轻松、舒服点
Because I have a little..
因为我有个小…
surprise for you.
惊喜要给你
Well, well, well. It must be 5:00 in Tulsa..
喔，喔，喔 土尔沙现在一定是五点…
because it's "sex o'clock" in N.Y.C.!
因为纽约现在是“六”点（音近性）！
Okay. This is how much I love you.
好了，这代表我有多爱你
The great white..
大白鲨…
Honey?
亲爱的？
Why am I watching a bunch of sharks swimming around?
为什么要我看一群鲨鱼游来游去呢？
Is this..? Is this not the good part?
这不是…？ 这不是你爱看的吗？
Do you want me to fast-forward to something.. toothier?
要我快转吗？ 转到露齿…比较多的地方吗？
No, I'm just not sure that you got the right movie, that's all.
不，我只是想确定 你是不是拿错了录影带
This is the only one they had at our video store.
录影带店里只有这一卷
Though they did have something called Crocodile Killers.
不过他们倒是有一部叫“鳄鱼杀手”的
Or does it always have to be sharks?
还是说，你非要鲨鱼不可呢？
Does what always have to be sharks?
为什么我非要鲨鱼不可？
Look, we can do something else.
听着，我们可以来点别的
Do you want me to get into the tub and.. thrash?
你要我到浴缸里…再用力扭吗？
- What's going on? - It's okay. It's okay.
-到底是怎么回事？ -没关系，没关系的
I still love you.
我还是爱你的
- Let me be a part of this. - Let me be a part of this!
-让我了解这一切 -是你应该让我了解这一切！
I saw what you were doing in Tulsa.
我看到你在土尔沙做的事
Angry sharks turn you on!
愤怒的鲨鱼让你“性”奋！
No, they don't.
不，并没有
Then why were you watching them and giving yourself a treat?
那为什么你一边看着他们 一边自己玩呢？
Oh, my God! When you came in, I switched the channel.
喔，天啊！当你一进来 我就转台了
I was just watching regular porn.
我本来只是在看一般的色情片
Really?
真的吗？
Yes. Just some good, old-fashioned, American, girl-on-girl action.
是的，只不过是一些正常 老套、美式的女对女动作片
Can I tell you how happy that makes me?
这件事真是让我太高兴了
You are an amazing wife.
你是个不可思议的老婆
Really, you are amazing. You were actually gonna do this for me?
真的，太不可思议了 你真的愿意为我这样做？
Where do you find the strength and the understanding for that?
你是怎么会有这样的 意志跟谅解呢？
I'm very, very drunk right now.
因为我现在非常、非常地醉
Ordinarily, I would talk to her, but my confidence is shaken.
通常我会去跟她搭讪的 但是我的自信已经动摇了
Did I sleep with her? Did I not sleep with her?
我有跟她上床吗？ 我没有跟她上床吗？
Maybe this is a wake-up call. You know, about your whole dating attitude.
或许该是你反省的时候了 检讨你的整个约会态度
You're in your 30s and you have never been in a long-term relationship.
你已经三十好几了 没有谈过一个长期的恋爱
Here you go from woman to woman..
女人从一个换到另一个…
meaningless experience to meaningless experience.
没有意义的关系 换到另一个没有意义的关系
Never even worrying that it doesn't turn into something more serious.
从不担心这些恋情都没有任何的发展
You're right. I love my life!
你说的没错，我爱死我的人生了！
I actually did sleep with her.
事实上我跟她上过床了